(Howard:)Getting Penny to go back out
with him after she dumped him.
(Raj:)Tricking Penny
into getting engaged.
(Howard:)And a few weeks ago,
he almost did a pull-up.
(Leonard:)I think
someone owes me an apology.
(Sheldon:)Well, don't feel bad.
(Sheldon:)I think we've all
been distracted
(Sheldon:)since the girls
entered our lives.
(Howard:)You admit Amy's a distraction?
(Sheldon:)Oh, very much so.
Listen to this.
(Sheldon:)This is from two days ago.
"Hi. Hope you're having
a good day."
(Sheldon:)Who has time
for this constant sexting?
(Leonard:)Well, maybe
we have lost our focus.
(Howard:)It wouldn't kill us to get
together and brainstorm ideas.
(Raj:)Ooh, we could have one
of those retreats.
Like our own science retreat.
(Howard:)My cousin has a cabin
out in the woods.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to a
cabin in the woods.
(Sheldon:)Did you see the movie
Cabin in the Woods?
(Leonard:)Then we'll go to a hotel.
(Sheldon:)A hotel?
Did you see The Shining?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
We could go up
(Raj:)to Big Bear
and get a house on the lake.
(Sheldon:)Did you see
The Lake House?
(Raj:)Nothing bad happens
in The Lake House.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, no,
not to them. To me.
(Sheldon:)Time traveling mailbox.
(Sheldon:)The only time that traveled
(Sheldon:)was an hour and half
of my life down the toilet.
(Leonard:)Fine. Then we'll just stay here
and do it.
(Sheldon:)Well, you didn't suggest
a beach house.
(Leonard:)You would go to a beach house?
(Sheldon:)Well, good Lord, no--
have you seen Jaws?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪